菩提字幕组
翻译: Wanna
校对: Ulysses
好的 孩子们 谢谢你们加入我
Ok, kids, thank you for joining me here
冷冻室欢迎你们
In the walk-in.Thank you all.
明明是你逼我们来的…
You said we had to, so...
我该把羊毛衫带上的
I should have brought my cardigan.
我有一个关于我们餐厅的消息要宣布
I have an announcement about the restaurant.
这个盒子里面 是特别的牛肉
Here in this box is the beef
它将要做成我们的… Gene 来点鼓声
That will make our--Gene, drumroll, please.
好了 够了
Ok, enough.
Gene
Gene.
这里 在这个盒子里装着的牛肉
Here in this box is the beef
将会做成我们的第10万个汉堡
That will make our 100,000th burger.
哇
Wow.
我能摸摸它吗
Can I touch it
我也想摸摸它
I wanna touch it, too.
我想用脚踩踩
I wanna feel it between my toes. Mmm.
我想插根炸药
I wanna put a stick of dynamite in it
然后把它炸飞!
And blow it up!
天呐 你们都怎么了
No. What is wrong with all of you
除了我 谁也不能碰这块肉
No one's touching this meat but me.
我也有个消息要宣布
I have an announcement, too.
胸罩擦着我疼
My bra is chafing me.
这不值得宣布
That's not a real announcement.
喔!我想到了一个
Oh! I have one.
我喜欢...
I love...
豪斯音乐
House music.
哇!我终于把它说出来了!
There! I said it!
我马上要拿到我的持枪执照了
And I'm going to get my gun license,
终于要拿到了
Finally.
喔 恭喜你
Oh, congratulations.
我简直不敢相信他们居然让你等了3天
Can't believe they're making you wait 3 days.
不要再抢白了!
Stop stealing my thunder!
我找到横幅了!
I found the banner!
是从那台旧印刷机那里找到的
It's from our old printer.
你只需要把旁边的小洞洞给撕下来
You just have to tear off the holes on the side.
我们早就该卖出10万个汉堡了
We were supposed to hit 100,000 ages ago.
呵呵 我们偏离计划了
Heh. We were way off.
是啊 真是一个值得纪念的日子
Yeah. Big time.
- 我能不能-- - 住手!
- Can I just-- - stop it!
就是它
There it is.
大家上!
Get it! Dive!
哦 我的天啊
Oh, my God.
请问你是第10万号吗
Are you number 100,000
不
no.
你对我生气了吗
are you mad at me
不
no.
喔 汉堡 你真可爱
oh, burger, you're cute.
你也很可爱啊
you're cute, too.
哈哈我不可爱
heh. I'm not.
喔Linda!
Whoa. Linda!
有人来采访我们了!
I think the news is here!
他们应该已经听说了我们的第10万个汉堡!
I wonder if they heard about our 100,000th burger!
什么!
What!
你好能为你们做些什么吗
Hi. How are you Uh, what can I do for you
你是Bob吗
Are you Bob
呃 是的 没错
Uh, yeah. I am.
我是Randy Watkins
I'm Randy Watkins,
我是个纪录片制作人
The documentary filmmaker.
好的 呃...
Ok. Uh...
我们正在制作一部关于牛肉行业的电影
We're making a film about the beef industry.
我听说你们将要卖出
I heard you were about to hit
你们的第10万个汉堡
Your 100,000th burger,
所以我想要跟你握一下手
And I wanted to shake your hand.
喔 好的 嗯...
Oh. Yeah. Um...
因为先生 你的手上沾满了鲜血
Because you, sir, have blood on your hands.
哟.这是番茄酱吗
Eww. Is this ketchup
这是被10万头被屠杀的牛的鲜血
It's the blood of 100,000 slaughtered cows.
你怎么弄我一手番茄酱
You ketchuped me.
我们在此是为了让你面对你的受害者
We're here to force you to face your victims.
看看你的牛肉
Meet your meat.
我勒个去~
What the hell
她叫Moolissa
Her name is Moolissa.
5天后将被杀掉
She's due to be "processed" in 5 days, Bob,
除非你选择留下她的生命
Unless you choose to spare her life.
- 什么 - 没错
- Wh-why  - That's right.
你将决定她的命运
You will decide her fate.
这是一部奶牛生命倒计时器
It's a cow...Ntdown
我们要看看当你面对汉堡
We'll see what your conscience tells you
你的良心会作何反应
When you're looking your burger right in the eye.
喔!这真是荒谬
Ow! This is ridiculous.
做汉堡又不是犯罪
It's not a crime to make burgers.
我们的手上没有沾满鲜血!
There's no blood on our hands!
你们在吵什么呢
What's all the yelling about
原来爸爸一直用死牛肉做汉堡
Turns out dad's been putting murdered cows in our hamburgers.
还把我们变成了帮凶!
And you made us a part of it!
你让我感到恶心
You make me sick.
孩子们 不要这样
Kids, please.
喔 看啊 奶牛
Oh, look. A cow.
你好啊 金发小姐
Hello, blondie.
啊哦 我把牛肉弄到你身上了
Oops. I got some meat on you.
死牛的肉放在活牛身上 真恶心
Dead cow on live cow. Gross. Heh heh.
哦 天啊
Ohh. God.
呃...你最好还是别说话了 Linda
Uh, not a good time, Linda.
Randy 别拍了
Randy, stop. Stop filming. You know,
我们不想再出现在什么奶牛纪录片了
We're not gonna be in your cow documentary anymore.
啊哦 你别无选择 Bob
Well, you don't really have a choice, Bob,
因为我们会坚持为动物伸张正义
'cause I stop at nothing to expose injustice to animals.
那个假发是用胶水粘上去的吗
Is that wig glued on
是的 这是--唯一能让假发定型的方法
Yeah. It's-- it's the only way it would stay put.
为了拟人化一下
It's to, uh, humanize her.
这真可爱
It's cute.
嗯我见过更可爱的
Mmm. I've seen cuter.
老实说 她只能算上是第4可爱的
Honestly, she's a 4.
Randy 我--我不知道该从何说起
Randy, I--I don't know where to begin.
首先 它不是一头母牛
You know, this isn't even a female cow.
牛肉取自犍牛 也就是阉掉的公牛
Beef happens to come from steers, which are male cows.
那么 呃 你怎样解释那个乳房呢
Then, uh, how do you explain that udder
喔 多大的乳房啊
Whoa. What an udder.
离开那里 Tina
Get away from there, Tina.
那个 呃 那不是乳房
That's, uh, not an udder.
喔 不是吗
Oh, it's not
不要听他的 Randy
Don't listen to him, Randy.
你可以去那给那头牛挤奶
You go ahead and milk that cow.
- 好好挤哦 - 我们已经挤过了
Milk it good. Oh, we did.
你不该这样做 那儿挤不出奶
You shouldn't have. Milk doesn't come out of that.
可是已经挤出来了 就在桶子里
Somethin' came out of it in that bucket over there.
你说的是这个尿桶吗
You mean this bucket of urine
尿 我还是认得的
I know urine, and that's urine.
- Gene 把桶放下 - 不!
- Gene, put that down. - No!
好吧 它当然闻起来像尿
Well, it certainly smells like urine,
但那可能是因为她生病了
But that's probably because she's sick.
不 她并没有生病
No, she's not sick.
因为你的行为而生病的 Bob!
Sick of your practices, Bob!
既然如此 我现在就去通知动物管理部门
Ok. You know, we're gonna go inside and call animal control,
然后你们将不得不离开
And then you'll have to leave.
你们已经拿到了许可证
Ok, so you've got all your permits,
允许使用此地吗
And you're renting this storefront
是的 哦 没错
Yes. Oh, yeah.
还有 呃 这头牛已经注射过所有的疫苗了吗
And, uh, this cow has had all its shots
是的 嗯 嗯 嗯 嗯
Yes. Sure, sure, sure, sure.
很好 我的工作已经完成了
All right. Well, uh, great. My job is done.
再见了
I'll see you guys later.
拜拜 管理员叔叔
Bye. Bye. Bye, animal man.
- 什么 - 喔 你可以在这里签字
What Oh, will you sign
表示同意在此电影出镜吗
A release to be in the movie
喔 拍电影 当然愿意
Uh, yeah. A movie. Yes.
你将会成为一个明星!
You're gonna be a star!
- 打扰下- 谢谢
Excuse me. Hello. Thank you.
- 我是那个打你电话的人 - 谢谢你
- The person who called you. - Thank you.
你不能允许把牛放在人行道上 这很危险
You can't have a cow on the sidewalk. It's dangerous.
先生 这头牛唯一的危险之处就是
Sir, sir, the only thing dangerous about this cow
她太可爱了
Is how adorable it is.
- 用手摸摸它 - 为什么
- Put your hand on this cow and touch it. - What
这只会对你有好处
I just know that that's gonna help you.
去摸那头牛
Touch the cow.
摸那头牛 那头牛
Touch the cow. Touch the cow.
- 我要离开这里 - 摸摸它
- I'm walking away. - Touch it.
好吧 尽管逃跑吧 你这个顽固的人!
Oh, right. Run away, tough guy!
就是! 去洗一个牛肉澡吧!
Yeah! Go take a meat bath!
或者干点其它残忍的事情吧!
Or whatever it is you people do!
电影”dial’m’for mooder” 采访一 镜头1
"dial 'm' for mooder," interview one, take one. "dial 'm' for mooder,"
ma ma ma ma
mi mi mi mi 好啦
mi mi mi mi perfect.
你认为牛应该被绞碎变成食物吗
Do you think cows should be ground up for food
坦白说 我无所谓的
Personally, I don't really care,
但是我爸喜欢把牛肉碾碎
But my father, he loves grinding them up.
要给他点颜色 让他清醒清醒
Gives him a rush. Makes him feel alive.
爸爸是一个很坏 很坏的人
Daddy's a bad, bad man.
这部电影会有配乐吗
Is this movie gonna have a score
你知道的 那种震撼人心的音乐
You know, some music to tug at the heartstrings.
我--我还有没想过这个问题
I--I haven't thought about it yet.
那瞧瞧这个
Well, check this out.
考虑考虑吧
think about it.
Louise 你觉得这像什么
Louise, what does that look like to you
牛的便便 Tina 你真有眼光
Cow poop. Good eye, Tina. Good eye.
不 我指的是这个笑脸的形状
No. I mean it's in the shape of a smiley face,
就像是一个微笑符Like an emoticon.
你认为这头牛向你发出了一个微笑符
You think the cow is texting you an emoticon
还是用屁股发的 真有意思
With its butt. Very interesting.
也许这头牛正试图与我们交流
Maybe this cow is trying to communicate with us
这是它知道的唯一方法 就是便便
The only way it knows how, with its feces.
就像原始人一样
Like gram-gram used to do.
妈妈 如果为了实施一个伟大的计划
Mom, let's say you had a brilliant plan, but to execute it,
你需要用牛屎来写东西
You needed to write something using cow poop
你会怎么做
How would you do it
喔 这是脑筋急转弯吗
Oh. Is this a brainteaser
嗯 我会用一个冷藏袋
Hmm. I would use a frosting bag.
我们有这样的袋子吗
Do we have one
是的 在储藏室里
Yeah, in the pantry.
我答对了吗 答案是冷藏袋吗
Am I right Is it a frosting bag
我们会知道答案的 妈妈
We'll see, mom.
好啦 完成
Yeah. Okey-dokey.
孩子们 再见了
Bye, kids. Have a good day.
凶手凶手!
Murderer!
喔 你好 Randy
Oh. Hi, Randy.
眨眼和一个大大的微笑
Wink with open smile.
这个给我看的吗
Is this for me
一定是的
It has to be.
我应该做什么呢
What should I do
我应该给它回信吗
Should I text back
我走啦
Comin' through.
哦 不
Oh, no.
它真可爱 让人很有胃口
That's really cute. It makes me hungry.
亲爱的 我想吃汉堡
Honey, I want a burger right now.
你们这些人是怎么了!
What's wrong with you people!
是啊!你们这些人是怎么了!
Yeah! What's wrong with you people!
现在我们来讨论一下音乐预算的问题
Now let's talk about your music budget.
会是1百万吗
Is it a million
这里我们只需要一个扩音器
We only need one megaphone out here.
你知道你需要什么吗 你需要这个!
You know what you need You need this!
好好考虑吧!
Think about it!
哇 顾客爆满了
Wow. We're mobbed.
谢谢你们的纪录片
Thank you, documentary.
Linda 这个片子里我是个屠牛的反派
Linda, the documentary is about me being an evil cow killer.
凶手凶手!
Murderer!
喔 别这样 Bob
Oh, come on, Bob.
这不算什么负面消息
There's no such thing as bad publicity.
对我们反而是个机遇
This could be huge for us.
就像性爱录影带
Like a sex tape.
这是我们有史以来最棒的免费广告
It's the best free advertising we ever had.
不过 这还是有点凄凉
I know. It's almost sad.
谁凄凉了
For who
也许是那头牛吧
I don't know. The cow.
这头牛都成明星了
The cow's goin' out in a blaze of glory.
大家都没吃亏 Bob
Everybody wins, Bob.
也许你是对的
I guess you're right.
因为这牛看起来过得不错
I mean, looks kind of sweet out there--
享受时光 阅尽路人
Enjoying the day, meeting people.
你好 奶牛
Hi, cow.
我要吃了你
I'm gonna eat you.
哇 它能听见我们说话
Whoa. Can it hear us
别激动
Easy.
就像沙子经过沙漏
Like sands through the hourglass,
我的牙齿也会穿透你的脊背
There goes my teeth right into your back.
这是我老婆
That's my wife.
喔 Bobby 我还真有点饿了
Ah, Bobby, I'm friggin' starvin'.
谁能忍心吃这么漂亮的生物呢
Who could eat that beautiful creature
真为你们感到耻辱!
Shame on you!
你今天打算吃汉堡吗
Are you going to be eating a burger today
我们从来不敢想象吃任何动物
We wouldn't dream of eating an animal.
我们经营一家州际宠物园
We run a petting zoo by the interstate.
名叫鹅妈妈打折宠物园
It's called mother goose's discount petting zoo.
羊马当宠物
Petting horses, goats, and sheep.
超值又划算
Precious memories on the cheap.
它实际上是个动物避难所
It's basically an animal sanctuary...
是我们捐钱建造的
That we make money off of.
没错
Exactly.
Randy 谢谢你们的工作
Oh. Hey, Randy, thanks for the business.
喔 嘿 Bob 不用谢
oh, hey, Bob, you're welcome.
好吧 我要去睡觉 你干嘛去
Well, I'm gonna go to bed soon. What are you gonna do
喔 我也要睡觉了 毕竟我也是个普通人
Oh, I'll probably go to bed, too, 'cause I'm a person.
再见
Bye.
Moolissa 小心!
M-Moolissa, watch out!
不!
No!
把犯罪嫌疑人带上来
Bring in the accused.
够了 够了
Yeah, yeah.
Louise 你来给我辩护吗
Louise, you're defending me
这个所谓的”人类”被指控
This so-called "man" stands accused
谋杀价值将近10万个汉堡的牛
Of murdering nearly 100,000 hamburgers worth of cows.
我代表Moolissa起诉你
I call to the stand Moolissa.
反对!
Objection!
那头牛正在假装它受伤了!
That cow's faking his injuries!
我能够证明
And I can prove it.
看着
Think fast.
驳回
Overruled.
Moolissa 请问凶手
Moolissa, is the man who killed you
现在在场吗
In the courtroom today
是我!
It's me!
是我杀的
It's me.
我只是个做汉堡的
I just make hamburgers.
从没想过会成为屠牛者
I never wanted to be a cow killer.
我对不起你…
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
哇 睡的真死
Whoa. Heavy sleeper.
什么--发生什么事了
Wha--what happened
怎么了 怎么了
What's the matter What's the matter
回床睡觉吧
Go back to bed.
不好意思 你快躺下睡觉吧
I'm sorry. Go back to bed.
嘿!Randy!
Hey! Randy!
你的牛快要冻死了!
Your cow's gonna freeze to death out here!
Randy!
嘘 安静
Shh. Easy.
安静 后退 后退 后退
Easy. Back up. Back up. Back up.
喔 我的天啊
oh, my God.
- 别紧张 - 牛!
- Heh. I know. - It's a cow!
其实 你不必知道它在这的
You know what You won't even know it's here.
看来于事无补了
Uh, that was like that already.
我会清理的
Definitely clean that.
啊哦 注意
Oop. Step back.
这是我做过的最棒的梦!
This is the best dream I've ever had!
人人都在地板上尿尿吧!
Everybody pee on the floor!
谁要加入!
Who's with me!
好啦 趁热赶紧吃吧
Ok, eat while it's hot.
喔 喔 喔 看看谁把麦片泡这么好
Well, well, well. Look who's too good for cereal now.
他想讨好那头牛
He's trying to impress the cow.
别瞎说
Don't be ridiculous.
居然有人会清理
Someone knows how to treat
一头性别不明的牛的尿
A lady-slash- male steer.
Bob 这种情况我觉得不舒服
Bob, I am not comfortable with this situation.
Lin 我有什么办法
Lin, what was I supposed to do
我做了个疯狂的梦 昨晚下雨的时候
I had that crazy dream. It was raining.
我的梦才疯狂
Well, I had a crazy dream
梦里没有什么牛pi-gu
That there wouldn't be a cow's a-s-s
在我吃早饭的时候对着我
In my face when I'm eating my breakfast.
我知道那个拼出来是什么单词
I know what that spells.
- 屁股 - 屁股
- Ass. - Ass.
妈妈
Mom.
- 是屁股 - 别再说了
- Ass. - Stop it.
说再见吧 各位
Say good-bye, everybody.
它要出去了
It's going out
到它该去的大街上去
On the street, where it belongs.
当然当然
Of course, ok Of course.
早饭过后我就把它牵到大街上去
Right after breakfast.
但牛是不会下楼梯的
Cows can't go down stairs.
- - 什么 - 什么意思
- What - What's that
牛是不会下楼梯的
Cows can't go down stairs.
大家都这么说
That's, like, a thing.
我听说过
I've heard that.
这就像一个有趣的事实
It's like a fun fact.
Bobby. Bobby
Bobby... Bobby...
难道牛不会下楼梯吗
Cows can't go down stairs
别告诉我这是真的
That better not be true.
你们怎么看
What do you know
我们就看见你推了半个小时牛屁股
We know you'll push on a cow's butt
并且没有求助
For half an hour without asking for help.
你打算一个人处理吗
Gotta have that butt all to yourself.
嘿 Bob! 发生什么事了 伙计
Hey, Bob! What's the deal, man
你对Moolissa做了些什么
What'd you do to Moolissa
它在上面 过来把它弄出去!
It's up here! Come get it out!
Linda, 它不再这里 Randy.
Linda. Uh, it's not up here, Randy.
我的老婆疯了
My wife's crazy.
如果他知道我把那头牛弄进来了
If he knows I brought the cow in,
他会认为他赢了
He'll think he won.
他赢了又怎样
So what if he won
你立刻把牛弄出去
Get the cow out of the house now.
- 不要说了 - 你赶快把牛弄出去
- Stop. - You get it out of the house.
- 我正在努力-- - 把它弄出去
- I'm trying to-- - come get--
喔呃 这头牛啊
Oh. Uh, this cow.
这头牛 是的 它确实在这里
This cow, yeah, is here.
爸爸 我弄了泡泡浴
Dad, I ran that bubble bath
给你和Moolissa的 正如你所愿
For you and Moolissa like you wanted.
泡泡浴!
Bubbles!
我会跟Moolissa一起洗澡 Randy
I'm not taking a bath with Moolissa, Randy.
只剩下2天了
2 days left.
只剩2天来决定是把这头牛送去屠宰场
2 days to decide to send that cow to slaughter
还是承认你是一个伪君子和凶手
Or admit you're a hypocrite and a murderer.
哇 多棒的电影啊
Wow. What a movie.
Bob电影不错
Bob, what a movie.
这不是我的电影 Teddy
It's not my movie, Teddy.
什么 难道他们只是
What, are they just
手持相机的酱油男吗
Followin' you around with a camera
你在镜头里 你是明星
You're in it, you're the star,
但这不是你的电影
But it's not your movie.
祝你好运 伙计
Heh. Good luck, guys.
- 能签个字吗 - 当然
- Will you sign a release - Sure.
要我的全名John K. Hancock吗
Do you want my John K. Hancock
- 是的 - 随便签哪吗
- Yeah. - Anywhere
不 签在这条线上面
No. O-on the line here.
我真该适应当明星 对吧
Better get used to this, huh
我要上电影了
Gonna be in the movies. I--
赶紧签在线上就行
Just on the line. Just on the line.
- 签在哪里都行吗 - 是的
- Right-- so anywhere - Yeah.
不!不! 签在横线上
No! No! Where it says signature!
好的 你叫什么要签你的名字吗
Ok, what's your name Do you want it to you
- 不 我 - Teddy,你在干什么啊!
- No, I-- - Teddy, what are you doing!
我正在给粉丝签名呢 Bob
I'm signing here an autograph, Bob.
多幸福的家庭
one big happy family.
大家在一起的感觉真棒啊
Isn't this nice, all of us here together
- 不 - 今晚 你会给我
- No. - Are you gonna give me
一滩便便 跟我说话吧
A poop tonight Talk to me.
Bob
Bob, huh
喔 这多好啊 她们处得不错
Well, it's nice. They like each other.
这对Tina来说是好事
It's good for Tina.
来吧 只要放轻松然后 噗--!
Come on. Just relax and--pbbbt!
只要这样我们就能交流了
It's all about the communication
你好 Moolissa
Hi, Moolissa.
生气的脸
frowny face
我待你不薄
All I've been is super nice to you,
这就是你的报答吗
And this is the thanks I get
亏我这么爱你
I loved you.
就像爱马一样
I loved you like a horse,
马是我最喜欢的动物
Which is my favorite animal.
我们还是就此打住吧
You know what Let's just stop
省的说出要反悔的话
Before we both say something we'll regret,
例如马比牛要好之类的
Like that horses are better than cows.
我现在后悔了
I regret that.
不过马确实比牛好
But it's true.
牛去哪了
Where's the cow
你是不是想问 小阉牛哪去了
I believe you mean, "where's the steer "
对 别忘了那是头公的
Yeah. Don't forget about that penis.
没错
Yeah.
Moolissa
哈! 牛可以下楼梯
Ha! Cows can go down stairs.
你需要的东西是4个羊毛袜子
All you need is 4 wool socks,
一个床垫 以及一个意念
A mattress, and the will to make it happen.
你居然…
You didn't.
你的女朋友已经被绑在外面了
Your girlfriend is tied up outside.
不--!
Nooooo
爸爸怎么了
What's wrong with dad
我觉得他是讨厌绳子
I think he hates leashes.
这不是我的错 Randy
It's not my fault, Randy.
她被人偷了 这不能怪谁
She was stolen. I mean, it's no one's fault.
除了Linda
Except for Linda's.
我必须这么做
I did what I had to do
为了保护我的家人和地毯
To protect my family and my carpet.
随你怎么说 那到底是谁
Yeah, whatever. So who do we know
会偷一头带着金色假发的牛
That would steal a cow in a blonde wig
一定是怪胎 呵呵
Maybe some perverts. Heh heh.
昨晚我们吵了一架 我和Moolissa
We had a fight last night, me and Moolissa.
真希望我们能回到从前
I just wish I had a chance to make things right again.
如果你知道了便便的真相 就不会这么想了
You wouldn't if you heard some of the things she was pooping about you.
嘿 伙计们!
Hey, guys!
看看这个!
Take a look at this!
...超值廉价
...On the cheap.
你们就这样一天到晚
You fellas just leave her tied up
把她绑在这里吗
Here at night all alone
喔 是的 是的她不会介意的
Oh, yeah, yeah. She doesn't mind.
我们可以找辆拖车… 对吧
We could just back a trailer right up here, honey, huh
我们当然可以 给我们自己再弄头牛
We sure could, get ourselves a cow.
没错 再弄头牛
Yeah. Get ourselves a cow.
是啊 再弄一头--
Yeah. Get ourselves a c--
真是混蛋
What a dump.
真恶心 嘿 她在那
Yikes. Hey, there she is.
喔 亲爱的上帝
Oh, dear God.
喔 飞跃月球的牛
oh, the cow that jumped over the moon.
看 这真棒
See, that's nice.
我们去把她弄回来
Come on. Let's go get her.
我们应该在天黑之后再过来
We should come back after dark.
为什么 因为这更富有戏剧性
Why It's more dramatic.
- 这真是愚蠢 - 不…
- That is stupid. - No. No, no, no.
太令人期待了 大拯救行动
I can see it now, the big rescue.
我们将用红外摄像把整个过程拍下来
We'll shoot the whole thing in infrared.
喔 Randy 不要--什么 用红外线摄像
Oh, Randy, com-- in infrared
这真蠢
This is nuts.
孩子们现在应该在床上的 Bob
The kids should be in bed, Bob.
这可是红外摄像机 Lin 给她看看
It's infrared, lin. Show her.
你干嘛要发出这样的声音
Why are you doing that
我这是在发暗号
I'm signaling.
各位 迂回前进
Everybody, serpentine.
太棒了!我们像支特警队!
Yes! We're a unit.
爸爸 你要记住
Dad, you should know
不管发生什么
If anything happens,
我们随时准备进攻
I am in full attack mode right now.
我也是 我极度渴望鲜血
Me, too. I'm hungry for blood.
还有糖果
And also candy.
喔 谢谢 孩子们
Uh, thanks, kids.
糟糕 我忘了起立的信号
Damn it. I missed the signal to stand up.
不好意思 各位
Sorry, everybody.
你让我们小队丢脸了
You let down the unit.
我说了对不起了
I said I'm sorry.
Bob 我们现在该做什么
Bob, we're here. What do we do now
我们 呃 呃 打开门
We, uh, uh, open the gate.
这不难
That was easy.
你们在干什么
What do you think you're doing
Gene 进攻!
Gene, attack!
喔! 小屁孩居然咬我的腿!
Ow! Your children are biting my legs!
Randy 去牵Moolissa 我们行动
Randy, get Moolissa. Let's move.
击个掌 Bob 我们成功了
High-five, Bob. We did it.
干得好 Randy.
High-five, Randy. Nice job.
要不是孩子们拖住那女人 我们成不了
I mean, we couldn't have done it without the kids biting that woman.
她满身木屑和山羊味
She tasted like sawdust and goats.
3, 2, 1.
3,2,1
Bob 生命倒计时器结束了
Bob, the cow-ntdown's over.
是时候决定Moolissa的命运了
It's time to decide Moolissa's fate.
认真的吗
Seriously Right now
我们刚刚才救了她
We just rescued her.
她该被送去屠宰场了 Bob
She's due at the slaughterhouse, Bob.
你的决定是什么
What's it gonna be
凶手!
Murderer!
Louise 闭嘴
Louise, shush.
Randy 能暂停拍摄你那愚蠢的电影一分钟吗
Randy, can you stop making your stupid movie for one minute
然后做个正常人
And just be a human being
什么 Bob难道你就不能暂停做你那愚蠢的汉堡
I don't know, Bob. Can you stop making your stupid burgers
1分钟 然后做个正常人吗
For one minute and be a human being
你是想让感到内疚吗
So now you're gonna guilt-trip me
这正是这部电影的目标
That's what the whole movie is about.
我还以为我们现在是朋友了,Randy
I thought we were friends now, Randy,
因为我们一起救了那头牛!
'cause we saved the cow together!
也许像我这样激进的纪录片制作人
Maybe activists- slash-documentarians
本来就不能拥有朋友 不管你救了多少牛!
Can't have friends, no matter how many cows they save!
好吧 这真令人伤心 Randy!
Well, that's just sad, Randy!
我知道!
I know!
喔 天啊 差一点就撞上了
Oh, my God. That was close.
我不知道我会做什么 如果
I don't know what I would do if anything
它发生不测…
Happened to moo--
啊 我没有撞到她!
Ahh. I didn't hit her!
我没有撞到她! 我--我刹车了!
I didn't hit her! I--I stopped!
她应该没事
She's probably fine.
她死了 刚才肯定心脏病突发了
She's dead. She must have had a cow heart attack.
- 不 - 听着
- No. - You know what
我现在要拿点东西
Let me get something out of my van real quick.
马上回来
Be right back.
Moolissa!
喔 我的天啊 不
Oh, my God, no.
你不要再我面前死去
Don't you die on me.
你不要死啊 说话啊!
Don't you die. Say something!
Louise 看啊 这是一个心
Louise, look. It's a heart,
一个心型的便便
A heart-shaped poop.
怎么回事 不是我弄的啊
What the hell I didn't do that.
我要把它保留下来
I'm keeping it.
Bob 没事吧
Bob, you all right
你的脸色有一些苍白
You look a little pale.
我们死了吗
Are we dead
我死了 Bob你只是晕过去了
I'm dead, Bob. You just fainted.
我晕过去了 哇
I fainted Wow.
- 这真是令人尴尬啊 - 好吧
- That's embarrassing. - Ok.
我--我不是容易晕的人
I'm--I'm not a fainter.
- 是啊我--我已经死了- 是啊
Yeah. I'm--I'm dead. Right. Yeah.
但是听着 我想让你帮我做些事情
But listen. There's something I want you to do for me.
用我的肉做汉堡包
Make burgers out of me.
什么! 不当然不行
What! No. No way.
当然可以 Bob
Yes way, Bob.
听着 自从我见到你之后
Look, ever since I met you,
做汉堡就让我觉得自己是个大坏蛋
Making burgers makes me feel like a horrible person.
Bob 我是一个阉割过的公牛
Bob, I'm a castrated steer.
是啊 我是一个已经结婚了的男人
Yeah, I'm a married man.
好吧真是有点幼稚--
Yeah, I'm kid--
咱俩都一样 对吧
Same thing, right
没错 听着
Yeah. Think about it, though.
虽然我是一头牛 你知道的
I'm a cow, you know
不是野马 也不是座头鲸
We're not wild stallions or humpback whales,
但是我们也希望自己很特别
But we wanna feel special, too.
起码我是这样希望的
I do, anyway.
是你让我变得与众不同
You turn me into something amazing.
慢着 难道这不是我的潜意识
Wait. Isn't this my subconscious
正在告诉我一些我想要听到的话?
Telling me what I want to hear
嘿 不是的
Hey, no.
实际上确实是在你的潜意识里
You know what Yes, it is, actually.
看来真有潜意识继续说吧
Well, it's working. Keep talking.
吻我
Kiss me.
不 我做不出来
No. I can't do that.
你可以的 而且你也想这么做
You can, and you want to.
好吧
ok.
就一下 很快的一下 因为这是我欠你的
One quick one because I owe you.
哦 还是算了吧 也许我-- 我们不应该这么做
Uh, maybe not. Maybe I--we shouldn't.
喔 我们应该这么做 完全应该
Oh, we should, absolutely.
喔 我的天啊 我到底在干什么
Oh, my God. What am I doing
你在干什么呢
What are you doing
我正要去吻一头牛
I'm about to kiss a cow.
没错
Yeah.
Bobby 你还好吗
Bobby, are you ok
爸爸的嘴在干什么呢
What's dad doing with his mouth
看起来他好像在亲吻
Looks like he's kissing.
呃 真丢脸
Well, this is awkward.
谁来拿个毯子遮住他
Somebody put a blanket over it.
味道棒极了
Tastes so good.
好的别看了 孩子们都进屋去!马上!
Ok. All right. Kids inside! Now!
哦
Ohh.
在Moolissa出现之前 我会说这只是牛肉
Before Moolissa, I used to say it's just beef.
我大大的错了
I couldn't have been more wrong.
牛是一种鲜活的生命
Cows are living creatures
它们有着美丽的毛发和棕色的眼睛
With beautiful hair and soft brown eyes,
还有柔软的嘴唇...
Soft mouths...
但同时它们也是牛肉
And also they are beef.
它们是统一的
They're the full package.
说这些是不是有点像伪君子
Does that make me a hypocrite to say that
- 是的 - 不 不是的 Randy
- Yes. - No, it doesn't, Randy.
如果真是伪君子 我也愿意伪一辈子
Or if it does, I can live with that.
下面正式推出我们的第10万个汉堡
I present our 100,000th burger.
第10万个汉堡!
100,000th burger!
真棒!
All right!
好的 展开横幅
Right. Undo the banner.
Bob的汉堡 10万个!真棒!
Bob's burger, 100,000! All right!
哇哦!
Hooray!
把横幅展开
Do the banner.
这是横幅! 横幅来啦!
Here's the banner! Here comes the banner!
我恭敬的称它为”安息汉堡”(或豌豆汉堡)
I humbly call this the rest in peas burger.
因为它里面有嘎嘣脆的豌豆和胡萝卜
Because it, uh, comes with snap peas and carrots.
谢谢你们
Thank you.
好啦 来参加葬礼的朋友们
All right, funeral people,
派对时间!
It's time to party!